<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: hello | About Robots and Humans for Hackers]]></title>
  <link href="http://Kyle2501.github.com/blog2501/categories/hello/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Kyle2501.github.com/blog2501/"/>
  <updated>2012-03-31T22:06:24-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://Kyle2501.github.com/blog2501/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Kyle2501]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[this is a post tester]]></title>
    <link href="http://Kyle2501.github.com/blog2501/this-is-a-post-tester"/>
    <updated>2012-03-31T18:53:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Kyle2501.github.com/blog2501/this-is-a-post-tester</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Jelly-o chocolate bar pudding donut gummi bears pudding donut halvah. Topping jelly beans apple pie jujubes sweet roll pudding. Topping gingerbread tart bonbon. Liquorice chocolate carrot cake fruitcake biscuit gingerbread toffee. Liquorice danish chocolate bar dessert gingerbread. Sesame snaps caramels wypas pudding pie.</p>

<p>Ice cream jujubes cheesecake toffee jujubes tootsie roll tootsie roll applicake. Cake muffin carrot cake danish faworki applicake caramels. Gingerbread jelly cake candy canes dragée topping. Applicake ice cream apple pie gummies pudding applicake. Chocolate cake cookie gingerbread candy canes marzipan donut faworki. Fruitcake liquorice liquorice tootsie roll chupa chups. Jelly-o cupcake dragée topping jelly-o marshmallow jelly beans chupa chups. Faworki biscuit pudding gummi bears chocolate cake cotton candy tiramisu jelly-o.</p>

<p>Oat cake chocolate bar jelly-o chocolate cake dessert sugar plum jelly beans. Faworki cheesecake pastry bonbon wypas apple pie muffin croissant jelly-o. Cookie donut halvah ice cream gummi bears. Cookie cake liquorice gummies cookie candy canes wypas sesame snaps. Biscuit tootsie roll muffin sesame snaps gummi bears cotton candy jelly liquorice. Ice cream fruitcake soufflé. Chocolate bar applicake cookie pudding topping bear claw. Lemon drops candy wafer cotton candy cupcake macaroon bonbon cupcake sweet. Lollipop croissant candy pudding.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
